{
  "2": [
    { "prompt": "me", "answer": "on" },
    { "prompt": "te", "answer": "out" },
    { "prompt": "e単", "answer": "eo" },
    { "prompt": "hi", "answer": "eo" },
    { "prompt": "on", "answer": "me" },
    { "prompt": "out", "answer": "te" },
    { "prompt": "eo", "answer": "e単/hi" }
  ],
  "3": [
    { "prompt": "me", "answer": "am eus" },
    { "prompt": "te", "answer": "ac'h eus" },
    { "prompt": "e単", "answer": "en deus" },
    { "prompt": "hi", "answer": "he deus" },
    { "prompt": "am eus", "answer": "me" },
    { "prompt": "ac'h eus", "answer": "te" },
    { "prompt": "en deus", "answer": "e単" },
    { "prompt": "he deus", "answer": "hi" }
  ]
}
